噢  我要紧张死了
Oh, this tension is killing me.
咱们的小宝贝可能就要摇身变成电影明星了
Our little baby could be a movie star.
不是可能  是一定
Not could be. Will be.
大家注意
Guys guys guys guys.
她停车了
She just pulled up.
全体人员  正常正常
Okay, everybody just act normal.
好的好的
Okay...
敢不敢更正常一点
More normal than that.
大家好
Hey guys.
哦  不
Oh no.
说回来  谁能比戈斯林和迪塞尔更出色呢
Oh well, who can beat Gosling and Diesel?
就是
Yeah.
丽芙鲁尼  就是我啊
Liv Rooney, that's who!
我拿到角色了
I got the part!
我要演特里斯坦莱肯啦
I'm gonna be Tristan Lycanth.
太棒了
(All cheer) This is amazing news!
绝对要庆祝一下
Let's celebrate!
狂欢一下
We need to party!
喔喔喔  狂欢
- Whoop whoop whoop! - Party!
我想  狂欢
- I want to... - Party.
我想  大伙  大伙
- I need to... - Guys, guys?
我真的真的真的很想
I really really really appreciate that,
但是试镜真的让我精疲力尽了都
but I'm pretty wiped out from the audition,
所以我还是去睡一觉比较好
so I think I'm just gonna go to bed.
晚安
Good night.
六  七  八
Six, seven, eight.
动起来  喔喔喔
- Party! - Whoop whoop whoop!